coppertradepro.com 2016-04-05

# CopperTradePro

An integral part of the relationship we have with our Clients is the information that you share with us. We want you to know how we treat your private information. Copper Trade Pro Limited protects our clients' privacy and does its best to provide their safety. Using Copper Trade Pro Limited website infers your consent to the data practices given in this statement. 

Copper Trade Pro Limited accumulates such personal data as your name, e­Currency wallet information, secret question, secret answer and e­mail address. We also need some details about your software and hardware, which are collected automatically by our site. We receive such information as the type of your browser, your IP address & time you access our website to maintain high level of our services and to manage the statistics of CopperTradepro.com. Please, be warned that if you reveal your personal data directly through the public message boards, we are not responsible for data privacy and third parties can use such data. We assure you that we do not read or interfere into your online private communication. Copper Trade Pro Limited "Privacy Policy" does not apply to other websites which you can decide to visit using a link from our website. That's why you need to read attentively their privacy statements before giving them the right to collect your personal information. Please be aware that Copper Trade Pro Limited does not bear responsibility for the content and rules of other websites. 

Copper Trade Pro Limited (CTP) accumulates your personal data and use it to ensure the operations on the website and to make appropriate provisions for your experience at our website. CTP also needs your personally identifiable data to inform you about other services or products you can obtain from us. CTP is also interested in your opinion and impression on potential new products and services that we may plan to offer you. In this case we may contact you via your e­mail. CTP does not share the information about its clients with other persons concerned. From time to time CTP may make you proposals on behalf of its business partners if the proposal seems to be interesting for you. In such cases your personal data (name, address, e­mail) will not be revealed to them. But this information can be given to authorized persons and partners for the purpose of helping us with our responsibilities for performance of our commitments. All of such third persons understand the importance of the clients' personal privacy and they are under duty of confidentiality. CTP does not reveal such information about our client as his/her nationality, political or religious affiliations without their permission, or misuse it. CTP monitors the websites and pages which are visited by our clients within personal script system (PSS). It is necessary to define the most popular services of CTP. This information also helps to offer customized content and to advertise within CTP to those customers who demonstrate interest in the subject. 

CTP guarantees the safety of your personal data in a safe environment and protects it from improper access, unlawful use or revealing. The use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol, protects your personal data at the time of transmission to other website. 

So­called "cookies" are used at the our website to help you in personalizing your online presence. A cookie means a text file, which a web­page server places on your hard disk. Cookies pose no threat to your computer: no memory leak, virus infection or other undesirable results can be expected. Only web­server in the domain, which issued it to you, can read it, because cookies are uniquely assigned. One of the main purposes of cookies is saving your time, which is very convenient for you. Cookie is intended to signal the web­server that the user has returned to a particular page. For instance if you registered and personalized on the CTP website to use its services, the cookie is necessary for the website to recall some particular information at your following visit. The process of your personal data recording becomes more simple and easier. Such data may include billing addresses, shipping addresses, etc. When you come back to the CTP website again, the data you conveyed before can be restored. In this case you get quick access to the necessary CTP website features. You can accept and decline cookies as you like. Most web browsers allow cookies by default, but usually you have an ability to set your browser to reject cookies if you want to. But if you make up your mind to reject cookies, you may fail to use all the interactive features of our website to the full as well as the features of other websites. 

CTP reserves the right to amend occasionally this "Privacy Policy" to correspond actual company's and customers' interaction. CTP strongly recommends you to review this Statement from time to time not to miss the updates. In this case you'll be always aware of CTP safety methods towards your personal data. 

CTP is glad to receive your comments concerning this "Privacy Policy". In case you think that CTP does not follow the rules and violates this Statement, contact us at support@coppertradepro.com We guarantee that we will take commercially reasonable efforts to discover and solve the problem.

**It’s Time to Expect MORE with CopperTradePro.com**
